Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Hi, I'm Nata, the baker.
I'm Nata the Candy Baker, and it looks like it's started.
I think it's started. I've been waiting for this... oh, here it comes! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Today, June 28th, Nata Kashiwanaga successfully made her solo debut.
Thank you very much!
Everyone's saying, "You're renting out the whole cinema!
We don't have money to rent out a movie theater.
Everyone calls it a movie theater.
I'll say "movie theater.
Sony's movie theater
It's a screening room.
Sony brought it to you.
When you're solo, you can use the cinema room.
I've never been here before.
I didn't know this kind of place existed.
Oh, you're doing this too?
He's working very hard.
He's a big newcomer... a big newcomer indeed.
This year, I've been here for 13 years.
What?
What? The picture quality is weak.
What? Image quality is weak.
As expected of a Sony camera.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Sony's camera is amazing!
Hey.
It's great!
Hey, guys.
You have a Nikamera? Yeah.
There are more cameras than people.
No, there are more people.
There are more people here now.
But there are more people.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I mean, really.
Until today.
I didn't know about this until today.
I didn't know about this place until today, because I thought we were going to do it in the conference room.
I didn't expect it, because I'm wearing this color, and I saw what you were saying on the screen.
It's flashy.
It was loud.
It's perfect.
People are saying, "That's the Sonny of the world.
Thank you so much! Ow!
It's like I just made my debut.
I'm doing it right, but the place is just...
I thought I had to do it right, like a stage theory, but I can't do it right, you know?
I'm not sure I can do it properly.
Thank God for the air conditioner on the wall to the left!
They say I'm a gachapin tomukku all by myself!
That's right.
Is this your home? If I had one like this at home, wouldn't it be amazing?
I wonder how many people he can invite.
50?
I don't want 50 people coming to my house.
No way.
I don't feel at home in a new place like this.
My restlessness comes out.
It's like a computer graphics.
I don't look like a CG.
Right now.
But it moves like this, like this, like this.
I know this isn't a composite, but it looks really composite.
I don't have any money, so it's a composite.
I was so surprised when I saw it with my own camera.
I was so surprised when I looked at it with my own eyes.
Orange, yellow, pink...
I thought they were all virtual backgrounds.
And you know what, it's got a microphone.
It's got a microphone!
It's a great delivery!
You know, I'm making my solo debut today, so...
At midnight.
My debut song "from about to to" was released at midnight.
Thankfully, a lot of people listened to it.
Have you listened to it?
Wait, more than 1,000 people have already seen it.
I'm afraid, I've delivered to more than 1,000 people like this...
What? Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! I'm just talking about what I saw in the press room.
I thought I should tell you how great Sonny is.
I thought the music was unexpected.
I'm sure it wasn't what everyone imagined.
I'm sure it wasn't the song everyone imagined, but it made everyone envious in a good way and betrayed them in a good way.
Oh, I was betrayed in a good way. That's what I wanted to say.
I want to say that I'm still listening to it and watching it.
Hearing your voice, your voice. Listen to my speaking voice.
If it was on speaker, it would be fine.
If you're wearing earphones and my voice is muted, you won't get the message,
You can't understand what I'm saying.
I said I thought it was R&B.I thought it was R&B.
I knew it. That's what I thought.
That's everyone.
That chick.
They love her too much.
She told me to shut up.
Me?
I'll shut up?
Stop it.
I can't wait to see the music video.
Yeah, I know, so it's almost 9:00 p.m.
9:00 p.m.
Excuse me.
I'm leaving.
Please wait for me.
I've never sung an enka before.
Why?
Why did you expect me to?
You never seem to say you love it.
I don't usually say it, so I had them put it in the lyrics.
That's right.
I'm looking forward to the show.
Yeah, now that... that thing.
You know, that Lime Music campaign.
And the invitations.
What?
That was so loud!
Congratulations on your major label debut!
Whaaaat! Thank you!
Congratulations!
Hey, what a surprise! I don't know...
This is... oh, cake!
Cake? Really? Oh, my God! Oh, my God, cake! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh my God...
Oh my God, I'm gonna drop this thing, it's dangerous!
Look at this!
Thank you! Thank you! We did it!
Sonny of the world congratulates me!
Yay!
I'm so happy.
Smells good.
What's with all the fancy stuff? It's got flower petals and stuff on it.
Oh, my God.
I'll eat it later.
I'm sorry.
Okay, let's all eat together.
Let's put the flowers on the side.
It's not CG.
Oh, my gosh! Oh, wow!
Sunflowers.
Sunflowers are in there.
Yay!
They asked me if I wanted a face cake.
I can't say I've ever seen such a beautiful plate!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
I didn't expect this celebration!
Yay!
It was really 12 o'clock!
Like, I made my debut too.
I was tweeting and instagramming and stuff.
I was posting on Twitter and Instagram.
I got a lot of congratulatory messages from many people.
I heard your song.
I've received a lot of comments
I've received a lot of comments.
You know!
Is it really six months since you graduated from the group?
Six months, you know,
I'm sure that in such a short period of time...
There aren't many solo artists out there.
I'm grateful to be able to sing again
I'm grateful to be in an environment where I can sing again
I'm really grateful to be able to sing again.
I'm also very happy that I'm starting to be able to sing again with all my fans who have been waiting for me.
I'm very happy to be able to start singing again with all my fans.
You wrote that we got off to a really good start, and I'm really grateful for that.
It's thanks to everyone around me.
Of course, we will be releasing our debut song and music video on June 28th, and we will also release our first EP and music video on July 12th,
Also, on July 12, we will be releasing our first EP, "From Here".
So there will be 5 songs including BOW2.
And we are coming out again.
Vow2, Emotional Warfare, and Those Days Bloom Next To You.
So I'm happy that I'm going to have more and more songs of my own from now on.
You know, when my mother heard Vow2
She gave me a very natural impression.
She said, "It's all chicks.
She said, "Of course it is.
That's right, she said.
But me too...
When we were shooting music videos and recording
I said I thought it was all Hina.
I thought it was Hina.
But the fans also...
Up until now, I sang with everyone and then we sang together, and then we sang together, and then we sang together.
And in the music videos, of course I'm in it, and then everyone else is in it, and then there's this solo.
So I was doing it solo.
I sang by myself to the group's songs and covered other songs on the occasion of my birthday, but I was doing it solo.I sang a group's song by myself and covered other songs at my birthday party.
But you know...
I had solo songs when I was a prawn.
But now that I've graduated and become a solo artist
We really started to write songs together
Together...
Is that what you call production?
Tazusa-ware? Tazusawa.
You mean you've been invited to be a part of it?
Let me be a part of it.
Let me take part in it.
Let me be a part of it? Anything.
Make it with me.
Together...
We'll decide on the songs.
I'd like to be a part of it.
Participation is the easiest way to use it.
You know, participation.
That's how we've come this far.
That's why
So, the music video, too.
The dancers were also very colorful, so the music video was very colorful.
I never thought I'd wear bright red, but I've never worn bright red, not even in my costumes.
The only bright red I've ever worn was that dress in the center, or something like that.
You don't get to wear bright red very often.
That's why I wore bright red today.
The way you show it.
I wore red.
And I wore this with red, too.
I was wondering why people were looking at me.
I wondered why they were looking at me.
It was because of this.
I was so glad that everyone was looking at me.
Thank you for looking at me!
Oh, I heard you wore red at the birthday party. That's right, I wore red for my birthday.
The nativity was bright red.
It was Christmas.
What do you mean?
Seriously, it was Christmas?
Christmas?
Red and green.
Me?
Yeah.
I don't know, it's just...
Well...
If it were dark green, it would be Christmas.
But this isn't Christmas at all.
I mean, it's not like it's Christmas.
It's okay to walk on Christmas.
Why don't we walk on Christmas?
Hey, it doesn't matter.
I wasn't really planning on wearing this red one.
I was going to wear those pink gingham pants underneath.
But right before I changed, I saw the music video that we're watching today.
I thought of red, so I decided to wear red pants.
Red pants
Red pants make me
My pants look like red.
I don't have red pants.
Pants
pants
I'm afraid of this pronunciation
I think it's best to call them pants.
I wanted to make the pants red.
I wanted to make them red.
That's all.
If someone says, "I'm scared of blondes and flashy clothes...
Everyone said, "Oh, I'm scared.
I'm used to being told I'm scary.
I've been told that too much.
I'm sure some of it is just a joke.
But if it's not a joke, I'm really sorry.
I'll make it a little less scary.
I'll make it less scary.
Oh my God, if I said pants red, what color are my pants now?
My pants are already transparent.
My pants are transparent.
Oh, my God, how much time do we have?
Not even close.
Mm-hmm.
It's about two tons.
Really?
Do you have a charger?
Oh, thank you.
Give me that.
I've been a little overconsumed.
Oh, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Oh, no.
I'm not panty-less.
That's all I'm saying.
When I said transparent, I meant panty-less.
Say that one more time and I'll make you stop.
Stop it.
People will say things like that.
Please stop.
Did you get any reaction from the audience from the members of Ebichu?
Who do you think?Who do you think I got that from?
Only one person responded.
But I did get one person on the phone.
He said, "Hey, it's Day.
And one said, "I heard your song.
and that he was so happy that it came up when he searched for "kashaginata".
There was one girl who had the same reaction as everyone else.
Let me guess...
It's all over the place.
Poe.
Maya and many others.
Yuno.
Mirei.
You're very fast.
When we talk about prawns, everyone is very fast.
It's because
It's because we're all sloppy.
You're kind of sloppy, aren't you?
Well... the correct answer is Mirei... but Mirei congratulated me on Twitter...
And then she sent me a line again. How kind of her.
There were a lot of Mayas.
That's my girl! Thank you!
Did anyone else drop by?
Did I get anyone else on line?
I just got a line from Kashiwagi Hinatsu!
It's official.
It was a long time ago.
She's not far away, is she?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
Hey, I just got this from a friend of mine who just sent me a youtube screencap of your debut.
He sent me a youtube clip of it.
I'm watching it.
But that's... that's Angulum's Rikako Sasaki Rikako.
Rikakora!
Congratulations on your debut.
That's very kind of you.
Oh, yeah, and the principal said on Twitter...
He said "Congratulations!
What do you mean?
Congratulations on your major label debut.
Why?
I said I'd do my best to work with you.
He said, "That's not the way to say it.
But you're my senior at the label, after all.
A little...
With this kind of seniority...
And there's also a senior brow artist.
I'd like to learn from them and do my best.
And Kimotsu-san, too.
And Poncha, too. He told me you asked him.
Thank you!
He wrote "Gyaru Oji".
I've heard about you and your sister on Twitter, and also, Izumi-san?
And Izumi-san? She was in the chorus of Momo's Momocross-chan, too.
And Izumi-san said...
I can't believe it.
I've come too far!
So many people have congratulated us.
I'm so grateful!
I'll do my best.
You said I told you too.
Thank you.
Thank you for looking at this.
Oh, my God, we're over 1,500 people. Oh, my God!
Fifteen hundred.
Let's go at our own pace.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Oh, I know, I know.
That's it.
What was that?
For this debut.
That's why I was interviewed at the beginning of June.
Well, today's debut...
I've been interviewed for a lot of things.
What?
Interviews and articles.
Natali was featured in one of them.
And CM Naa...
So I hope you'll check them out as well.
Oh, my God!
It's already about 30 minutes high?
MV
So fast!
I wonder what people imagine when they hear that song.
What's it like?
I don't know.
But what do you imagine? Because the teaser is already out.
I couldn't write much.
I said something stupid.
There's the red guy and the dorky guy, right?
That's right.
That's right! That's right!
That's the kind of music video I'm talking about... in about 30 minutes.
It's called the music video with the red sun going wild.It's called the music video with the red sun going wild.
Yeah.
What do you want to eat now?
they say...
Because he wrote a lot.
Ten years?
Ten years.
Nine years.
I've been reading for nine years.
It's interesting. It's a good example.
Yes, thank you.
When do you feel like an adult?
When I feel like an adult.
What? When do you feel like an adult?
What? Where is it? Not where.
What? What am I doing? You know, when I think I'm getting older...
I don't know.
I still think about it sometimes.
When I charge 10,000 yen to that watermelon...
I think "Oops".
I used to charge 2,000 yen.
I used to charge 3,000 yen.
But now it's 3,000 yen.
I'm fine with 2,000 yen, but 1,000 yen runs out quickly, so 2,000 yen is fine.
I take the train to work every day, but it's not that expensive.
I don't come from my parents' house, so it won't be that expensive.
So, 2,000 yen.
So maybe it's not 10,000 yen, but even 5,000 yen... I don't know, I'll charge 5,000 yen
I'm a little scared.
I charge 2,000 yen every time because it's 2,000 yen.
Maybe you feel like you're spending too much.
I wonder if 10,000 yen is better to prevent overspending How much does everyone else charge?
Don't you use a subscription?
I see... Ebisu...
I should make a subscription to Ebisu?
Is that faster?
Yes, it is.
But you go to Ebisu, right?
Because I have an office there.
What? Commuter pass?
Recently, I've been charging 5,000 yen.
3,000 yen is more than enough.
3,000 yen.
So if I drop the card, it's over in the morning. I use my cell phone's Mobile Suica.
But, you know, if there's a communication problem, like yesterday, you'll have a problem recharging the card.
That's 3,000 yen.
Thanks for letting me know.
Auto-recharge is the most dangerous.
You're using Wig, right?
I don't want to auto-charge.
I know you're wondering what I'm talking about... but we're down about 50.
Oh no, oh no!
MV, can I look? After? Can I? Look.
I'll get no reaction. Can I? Go ahead.
We're in a movie theater, and there's a huge screen right in front of us.
Yeah, it's on a computer, so I'll watch it on a computer.
I'll watch it on the computer.
What?
When I heard that, I thought, "We're going to watch it here.
Everyone says it's not fair.
Well, you can listen to the sound, everyone's already listening to it.
I kind of fell off the grid six months ago.
Sorry.
Just because it's you doesn't mean it's fair.
No? Can't I look?
I was in the first row.
Can't I look?
Uh-uh.
I think we should be together.
It's fine, you can look.
Hey, if we're going to be in an argument, why don't we just stand in a row, I'm in the front.
Everyone's in the back, so why not stand in a single file?
Everyone stand in a single file because, you know, it's dangerous to stand in a single file on the street
Just stand in a row.
It's safer.
Right?
I said it's fine.
Just 30 seconds at the beginning.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Are you saying that the concept of the shrimpers is not good? He said, "No, no, no, no, no.
That's not true.
The concept of Ebiichu is just a single horizontal line.
It's in the lyrics of the song Sudden Death.
I don't think the concept of "Ebichu" was that we are all in a row.
I don't think we had that concept.
Was there?
I don't know. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I apologize for earlier.
I left the horizontal row.
So we are in a vertical line.
I'm in the front, in the front, so I'll watch the music video.
See?
I feel sorry for the person at the very back, don't you? I'm told.
If we line up vertically.
Okay.
I'll react, everyone.
So...
I can hear the sound, okay?
Because there's one more thing.
There it is.There it is.
We don't have 30 minutes.
I'll get it.
This one right here.
There it is.
Okay.
What's that?
No, no, no, no, no.
How did you do that?
What's that? Did it come like this?
I don't know if you can keep up with me. I can't stop all day.
Okay! I like it!
I don't know what the lyrics mean.
The journey has begun.
I love it!
Thanks for watching!
I love it here!
It's great!
Great!!!
This girl is not NS.
I'm hurting.
You're so hot!
I'm married.
slipper chell
I'm confused
here
Leader
ll
by H.
Lion, lion, yes.
I love it. I love it pink.
Be the most fun in the world
Be my own life Be my own life
Be the best life Be the best life Be the best life
Be the best life Be the best life
I can't get enough of it, I'm gonna have so much fun
Be my own life Be my own life
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Ah, here it comes! It's okay, it's okay!
You were cute.
That was cute.
Good end, good end, good end.
It's okay!
Why are you stopping?
I'd stop if I did.
Okay, so I kind of saw it first.
What's up, guys?
I only heard the sound.
You know...
He said we can watch it again.
No, it's okay.
I'll watch it with you guys.
Everyone says they thought we were going for a second week.
All the way? We're watching it all the time.
From now on? The best part is, the man in red is in the show all the time.
The man in red is on the whole time.
The best part of the song is that it's not even three minutes long.
Maybe they cut it.
It's less than 3 minutes long.
And yet it's packed with so much music.
And look at M.B.I.
I'm sure everyone will see a lot of it.
It's not Kazu Laser, but a 24 year old girl in red all the way through.
2 minutes and 52 seconds.
Just like a cup of noodles.
If you could have left me with eight more seconds...
It would have been nice.
So, if you have your chopsticks and stuff ready, it'll just be a second.
Perfect.
I've been thinking about the songs lately, too.
Or the first and second verse are right next to each other...
It's nice.
This time it's all about dancing, dancing, dancing.
It's been a long time since I've seen a dance like that.
It's been a while since I've done something that's not idol choreography.
It's been a while since I've done a dance that's not idol choreography.
So of course it's cute.
Of course, there was a lot of cuteness and pop.
But you can also see the coolness that goes along with the song.
I thought it was really cool and in line with the song.
And this time, we had four dancers.
We had four dancers this time.
Why?
Well, listen... you'll be in the center the whole time when you're dancing.
We've never had a center dancer before.
Basically, there's a formation.
We move around, move around, move around...
I'm always in the center.
I was dancing in the middle of the song, and I was wondering if it's okay for me to just be in the center all the time.
I was doing the music video.
But I was wondering if it was okay for me to just be in the center all the time.
It's different now that I'm solo.
You're the center.
Is everyone dancing vertically?
Are you dancing vertically? I mean...
Was there ever a uniform vertical?
Oh!
I don't know.
I think there was.I think I had one.
If you said there wasn't, then there wasn't.
It only lasted a moment.
I know, right?
It's too short a time, too short a time, too short a time, too long a time, too long a time.
It's too late... how many minutes?
Yes!
I've got something I have to tell you.
It's time for an announcement.
I'm good at announcements.
Well, well, well... we're going to go live in just over 10 minutes.
I'd like to announce that I made my solo debut today, June 28th.
The song is called "From Bout to etc." and it's currently being distributed to rave reviews.
I hope you'll listen to them on the subscribe page and watch the mv afterwards.
And on the 12th of August
We will also be releasing our first ep "From Here" on the 12th of August!
It will feature 5 songs including the debut single "from bow to toe".
from bow to toe, emotional warfare, those days bloom next to you, and the ep will be released on the 12th of July.
So soon, huh?
Two weeks, two weeks, and you can already listen to more songs.
And we're going to release our debut single "from bow to toe" on LINE MUSIC.
We're running a campaign called "Play count campaign" on LINE MUSIC, and we're going to draw lots from among those who listen to the song on LINE MUSIC.
We will give away a mini live & meet & grid for 240 people in total!
The more views you get, the more chances you have to win, so please listen to the song!
The campaign starts today, June 28th and ends on Tuesday, July 11th.
The Kashiwagi Prize
Kashiwagi prize is a mini live and Miiguri's Tokyo
120 people in Tokyo will win the prize on Saturday, August 12th from 1:00pm to 2:00pm.
And the Hyuga Prize will be given to 120 people at Mini Live and Miiguri in Osaka on the next day, Sunday, August 13th, also at 13:00 and 10:00.
We invite you to this event.
I would like to invite 240 people to this mini-live and miguri event.
And here it is!
This is it! This is it!
From 9:00 p.m.
We're going to start a music video campaign for the music video "from about to" and so on.
We're going to do it from now on.
We will be giving away a poster with the sign to 20 winners drawn from those who watch the music video of VAL2, which will be released from 9pm, and post a screenshot of your favorite scene on Twitter.
So, there are probably a lot of places where you can take screenshots. There are lots of places where you can take a screenshot, so please do it.
It's just a photo shoot. Everyone can do it, right? Take a picture and post it on Twitter.
I would like you to take a picture and post it on Twitter.
The campaign starts at 21:00, when the music video will be released,
You have two whole days to take a look around during the two days,
So please take the time to look around during the two days,
Please take a look around during the two days and post a screencap of your favorite parts.
The winner will receive a signed poster for 20 people. We will send them to the winners.
I'd like you to post your favorite scene from the music video, the YouTube link of the music video, and the hashtag of the campaign.
What would you suggest?
Let's decide now.
What's good?
Can I tweet as many as I want?
Can I have more than one?
Oh, just one per post, but multiple tweets are allowed.
You can't win more than one more round.
Oh, that's true.
If I tell that person 20 tweets, it's not good.
Don't do that kind of thing.
I've got it... and I want you to put those two hashtags, one hashtag, one hashtag...
Kashiwagi Hinata Underbar From Boutou and...
And one more, Yuba, with the hashtag "Ganbatte it up, Hinata!
Oh, Hinata's hashtag
Hinata's hashtag
Hinata's highlights
Hinata is a lot of hinata
There are so many Hinata hashtags!
Which hashtags are the easiest to understand?
Until now... when we decide on something...
Like "Hinata's something" or "Hinata's something".
Like, "Today is Hinata's debut.
There was something before, wasn't there?
I don't remember what it was...
Hyuga's pace...
Steam
It's all in the Hinata hashtag Hinata's something.
I'm trying to make it easy for even me to understand.
Let's make it a hyuga something.
A piece of Hyuga
A squiggle of Hyuga
Shall I make it the most obvious one?
Shall I make it a hinata no sukusho?
It's all in hiragana, right?
Okay then.
Hashtag Hinata no Sukusho
All in hiragana.
And the other one is hashtag kashiwagi hyuga
Kashiwagi Hyuga is fine in Kanji Kashiwagi. KashiwagiHinata, underbar from bow to toe
From bow to toe means from, bow, to, and to.
The first letter is capitalized.
Like from bow to toe.
You know what I mean?
Do you get it?
The initial accent is very important.
Toe.
Okay.
Well, I'm sure it'll come out after this.
I'll write something official or something.
I'll use that as a reference.
When the music video is released...
I'll write about it.Just a moment.
Enjoy the show.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, yes, yes.
Please use two hashtags, one for the loan and the other for the photo.
Please add the hashtags "underbar Fronboutou etc." and "Hinata no Sukusho." I'll copy and paste it into the tweet.
I'll copy and paste it and you can tweet it.
I'll copy and paste it.
How do you take a picture?
I don't know.
On the iPhone, you just press the power button and the button above the volume.
Press the power button and the button above the volume.
That's it!
I got a screen shot.
What? I don't know about Android.
I don't know anything about androids.
I don't know what android is
Android is a little bit...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Check it. It's a cell phone, check it.
How much time do we have?
I've been told by people I know that I don't look like a rookie. I should have looked like a rookie.
And his son says he's not a rookie, so Sho's son says he's not a rookie.
That's terrible!
I'm glad she's new.
I'm new. I'm going to be so flattered.
Please take care of her.
You probably don't wear this kind of clothes.
It's coming soon, right?
20...
Oh, no.
The music video won't be shown here on the live broadcast.
There's another...
music video... just the music video.
You can go there.
I'm waiting for you here.
I'm waiting for you all.
Three minutes... look! Three minutes, come on.
Three minutes is all it takes to get away from me.
Three minutes to get away from me for a minute.
Red... go see who's in the center the whole time.
I want you to.
I put the link in the description.
It's so sweet that they put the link in the description!
That's so sweet.
So I'll be gone at 9:00 p.m.
I mean, I'll watch the music video one more time.
I'll watch the music video one more time, and then everyone will come back, we'll have a little chat, and then I'll go bye-bye.
But I'll wait... and wait... and wait... and wait... and wait... and wait... and I want to hear what you think.
I'm waiting to hear what you guys think.
I'd love to hear what you think.
I'm going to use that hashtag on Twitter today or something.
Kashigahinata and the hashtag.
What's that? Hinata's debut.
And the hashtag "big newcomer.
Tweet me something!
Like, "Tweet me if you find anything...
I told her.
I hope you'll tweet about the music video
I hope you'll tweet about it.
Oh, I've got two devices.
Some people are saying they're going to watch it on that one.
He said he's going to watch the music video on his TV.
Yeah, on the big screen on the left.
He set the alarm to go off five minutes ago.
That's great.
He's asking if we can archive it.
Is it? He said yes.
It's only for a certain period of time, but we'll make sure. Well, today.
I know some of you can't see it.
Isn't it almost done?
Four minutes.
I'm so excited.
It's amazing that I'm the only one who can see it.
I don't know when I'll be able to do this.
I've been recording for a while now... and it's only their songs, of course, and they have their own parts, but I go in and sing the whole thing by myself.
I sang all the songs and took the harmonies and the chorus...
But now I'm solo, and I'm recording.
And when I heard the whole recording, not just the finished version, but the whole thing that we shot at the time, I was like...
Wow! It's all me! I was like, "Wow, it's all me!
That's when I realized that I could be a solo artist too.
I wonder when I'll be able to do music videos.
I can't wait.
I'm all alone.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Hey.
She said you got over 5,000 subscribers.
YouTube. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my God. Two minutes.
Oh, yeah! That's it! I made a playlist on line music.
I made a playlist of songs that make you want to sing and dance.
You can listen to it too, if you like!
I've included a few of my own songs, too, of course!I've included various of my own songs, of course!
It's coming soon, so get ready to go!
Even if it's just your fingers.
I'll get my phone ready too.
Yes, I put it in Yajima Beauty Salon.
I love it.
I love that...
I love the Japanese way of looking at things.
40 seconds to go. I love the power of the Goddess so much, I put in the power of the Goddess.
Get ready... 30 seconds...
I'm gonna stay here and wait for you guys, so just stay away from me for three minutes, please.
Please, I'll stay away from you.
I'll see you guys later. Everybody make sure you see the good stuff and stuff.
You're going to tell me what you think. Yes, five, four, three, two, bye! See you tomorrow!
Welcome back, everybody! I've been waiting for you!
I've been out for a while too.
My phone went crazy.
You were looking at me. Okay, I'm back.
What's going on?
The chat's missing, and all the comments.
What the hell?
What's this?
Oh, it's back.
So how was the music video?
How did you like the music video?
Thank you very much.
I'm a rookie, so I chew.
I'm so sorry.
It all happened so fast.
It went by so fast.
That's why I can watch it over and over again.
Shut up, my iPhone!
Stop talking.
Yes!
I like the part about the phone screen.
That part was fun.
I was really taking pictures the whole time.
I'm the one who didn't think they were using the iphone thingy, so I had them use the iphone thingy, and it's a 4-split.
I thought it would be too obvious. I was fine with it.
They told me to sing while doing aerobics at the show, and it's really, really tiring.
I was in love with her during the break.
And when they changed the camera settings...
It was freezing, so I did a little workout there, too.
He said the mike was too long.
You know?
It's so long, it's like a TV set.
The crew was holding it like this.
You know, at the beginning of the show, when they go to film something and take the microphone away from you?
I like that. The first time I did that, I couldn't get it done in time.
I couldn't get it done in time.
I jumped and the song started, so it looked like I was singing while jumping, but it's not.
The mv's used the right kind of music.
Hey guys, almost everybody came back to this video.
Thank you so much.
We also used a fisheye lens and some other things.
And playing with the camera lens.
The clothes are colorful and cute.
The clothes were colorful and cute, and the dancing was cool, and the choreography was cool, and everything was really fun.
I thought I'd be nervous, but I wasn't.
I thought I would be nervous, but I wasn't that nervous.
The director was also the director who shot the singalong singalong when I was a shrimp.
I was so happy to see him after a long time.
I'm very grateful.
I'm very grateful to have the opportunity to work with someone I've worked with in the past.
I'm really grateful to be able to work with him again as a solo artist.
I just made my debut today.
I will continue to do my best as a big newcomer.
I hope everyone will watch the rest of the video.
The music video
Please leave your comments on the music video.
It's strange to me that I have my own youtube channel and my own music video.
I'm so grateful for that.
Thank you so much, I'm gonna work hard, I'm gonna work hard.
Yay!
That's right, and the campaign for the screenshots.
The one I mentioned earlier. It just started.
Since MV has been released, we'll be running the campaign until 11:59 p.m. on the 30th, the day after tomorrow.
The hashtag is Kashiwagi Hinata & Bar From Now to the hashtag Hinata's screencaps.
Hinata's screencaps are all in hiragana.
I'll post them later.
The campaign will be a poster with her autograph on it.
So...
Kya!
The EP is coming soon.
And the live show is only a little over a month away!
only a little more than a month to go!
August
Mini-Live
Hey!
I'm happy to sing in front of everyone again.
I can already hear my voice.
I'm starting to regress more and more.
This song...
You can say whatever you want.
I'm not saying you can say whatever you want.
Don't yell at me or anything.
I don't like it when you yell at me.I don't want to hear the yelling.
But you know what, you can say something like...
You can say that to everyone.
Like, "Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can say that.
So after the mini live...
I can't wait to do the live show when the songs are getting better and better.
I'm sure everyone's excited about it, and I want to do it too, so I'm going to work hard.
I'm still working hard.
I'm still working hard on it.
But you can only win one ticket for each person who tweets it.
I'm very grateful for your kind words, but I'm not going to send 5 or 6 more tweets.
I'm not going to go for 5 or 6 more. I'm just going to get one if I win.
Is the poster the one with the black hair?
Yes!
It's a different person.
Yesterday.
Oh, and I've started TikTok, so please follow me. I'm working on it.
Please tell me what's trending already.
I'll tell you what's popular. I'll tell you all about it.
I'll talk to you.
Because I'm a heart bell
My mouth...
I've already told you what I'm going to tell you.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
Should I tell you what my favorite onigiri is?
My...
My favorite onigiri ingredients are salmon, tuna mayo and kelp.
And suji powder.
And cod roe and cod roe.
I like most of them. I love onigiri.
Because this is good.
Oh, grilled onigiri is good too
I want a grilled onigiri. I'll buy a frozen one.
No, tomorrow morning. Tomorrow morning.
I have to be up early tomorrow morning.
That's right. We're going to Sapporo tomorrow morning.
We're going to Sapporo for the campaign.
You coming?
I'm new. I've been miked. I'm sorry. I'm new, so I'll be doing a little campaigning.
I'm going to Sapporo tomorrow.
That's a sudden announcement.
I'm going on the radio tomorrow.
I'll be there!
I was wondering if you'd like to stop by Fukuoka? Or...
"Why don't you come by Nagoya?
He said come to Chiba.
I'm from my parents' place.
Not in Chiba?
Yeah, I'm going to Sapporo tomorrow.
I can't go to Escondido.
I can't.
I just told you for the first time that I'm going to Sapporo.
I haven't told anyone.
You know, that thing on the radio...
It was just on the radio.
I thought I should tell you. I thought I should tell you.
I was going to tell you.
So I'm leaving early tomorrow morning.
I'll call you guys when I go somewhere else.
Okay.
This is how it went down. My delivery.
I'm sure there may be some people who have never seen this before.
I'm really serious about doing this.
I can do it. I can do it, but I can't. I'm the type of person who does it.
I can't do it. I'm restless.
I ask weird questions right away.
But today is my debut day.
18 minutes before mv went live.
So I want you to watch mv a lot.
That's all I'm saying.
I'll be back.
Oh, what did you say?
My husband is a big fan. He wants you to come to Kobe.
Well, he is. Thank you very much.
So, when this is over, you guys watch Moven one more time.
And look for the good parts and take scans of them.
I hope you enjoy the music as much as I do.
We'll be releasing more EPs, mini-lives for the LINE MUSIC campaign, and more and more solo performances.
I'll be coming out with more and more solo projects...
Hi! I'll do my best.
I'm sure most of you have been supporting me since the group days.
But now that you've seen my solo work as well, you'll be able to support me in the future, too.
Whether or not you will continue to support me in the future depends on your feelings.
I'm sure that you will support me in the future.
I won't ask you to support me lightly.
I won't tolerate it.
So, please feel free to do so.
I want you to come and see the show and support us when you want to support us.
I hope you will support me, so please watch me with those warm eyes.
I'll do my best to be a big person.
I'll do my best to become a great person.
You always give me warm words, don't you?
I'm not alone... because you're all here... and I'm in the vertical position... so I might be behind you...
I'll do my best to make it look like I'm doing my best.
I'll hang it up like I'm the best.
Okay, that's it.
We're done.
I don't know how long the archive will be, but we'll keep it for a little while.I don't know how long the archive will be, but I'll keep it for some time.
Yes, and the mv has just been released.
I hope you'll take a look at the mv again, and the music, too.
I hope you can listen to it on the train and in many other places.
I'm sure you can listen to it on the train and in many other places, so please listen to it!
I know I only say I'll do my best, but I really have no choice but to do my best.
I'm really going to enjoy doing it at my own pace.
Let's have a great time together!
I made my debut today, and I look forward to working with you all in the future.
Okay, that's it, everyone. I'm off to Sapporo tomorrow.
I'm going to bed. Thank you very much.
Don't sleep and watch the music video.
Thank you very much. I look forward to working with you.
Bye bye.